<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-07-01T11:52:08+00:00</updated><id>https://daanvdweijden.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Welcome to my personal website! </subtitle><entry><title type="html">welcome</title><link href="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2024/welcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="welcome"/><published>2024-07-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-07-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2024/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2024/welcome/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="hello-everyone">Hello everyone!</h1> <p>I’m thrilled to announce the launch of my new PhD website. As a researcher in artificial intelligence, I have always been fascinated by the potential of technology to revolutionize the way we live and work. In this blog post, I’ll be sharing some insights into my research interests and what you can expect from this website.</p> <p>Throughout my career, I have been driven by a desire to use artificial intelligence for the greater good. Whether it’s developing more efficient algorithms or creating systems that can help us make better decisions, I believe that AI has the potential to transform our world in countless ways.</p> <p>My research interests are focused on natural language processing and human-centered machine learning. These fields allow me to explore how we can use AI to better understand and interact with human language, as well as create systems that are more intuitive and user-friendly.</p> <p>As I continue my journey through PhD studies, I am excited to share my research findings and insights with the wider community. Through this website, I hope to engage with other researchers, practitioners, and curious individuals who are interested in the latest developments in artificial intelligence and its potential applications.</p> <p>In addition to sharing my own research, I also plan to feature guest posts from experts in the field, as well as highlight some of the most innovative AI projects currently underway. I look forward to hearing your thoughts and feedback on this new endeavor.</p> <p>Thanks for stopping by!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[welcome]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Google Gemini updates: Flash 1.5, Gemma 2 and Project Astra</title><link href="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Google Gemini updates: Flash 1.5, Gemma 2 and Project Astra"/><published>2024-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing updates across our Gemini family of models and a glimpse of Project Astra, our vision for the future of AI assistants.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog"/><published>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</updated><id>https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://daanvdweijden.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>